TONNY OCHOLLA

telephone: (+254) 746 629007 email address: tonnyocholla@gmail.com

JUNIOR FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

BSc. in Business Computing graduate passionate about developing attractive, usable and interactive websites. Highly-capable leader having led a team in various roles while volunteering with AIESEC. Open to learning and further improving my skills in developing enjoyable experiences for users of the web.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

VueJs HTML CSS SASS Preprocessor Git JavaScript(NodeJs) MongoDB

PROJECTS

- SHORTLY. A responsive url shortening website that integrates with the shortcode api. Live website at https://shortly-ochollat.netlify.app/
- COUNTRYINFO. Website that pulls data about countries such as their capital cities, regions among others from <u>restcountries api</u> and displays it on the page. Live website at https://countryinfo-ochollat.netlify.app/

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Business Computing, Jomo Kenyatta University of Agriculture and Technology 2016 - 2021 High School Diploma,
Nakuru Boys High School
2012 - 2015
• Mean Grade - B+

CERTIFICATION

ES Fundamentals with SAP, SAP University Alliances(ESEFA)

July 2019 - August 2019

WORK EXPERIENCES

Ministry of Works Sports Club

Nairobi, Kenya Sep 2019 — Dec 2019

Technical Support Intern

- Gained knowledge on how to communicate technical jargon to members of different fields in an understandable manner.
- Maintained IT resources for the employees such as Point of Sale Systems, computers among others.
- · Assisted in troubleshooting issues and provided technical support.

EXTRA-CURRICULAR EXPERIENCE

AIESEC in JKUAT

Kiambu, Kenya Jan 2019 — Feb 2020

Team Leader in Outgoing Exchange Portfolio

- AIESEC is a global organization for young people to develop their leadership potential through international intenships and volunteer opportunites
- Organized sales drives that managed to increase the organization's visibility in the university by 30 % from the previous year
- Liased with international partners for exchange experiences in Egypt and India.

Team Leader, Annual Parents Conference for AIESEC in JKUAT

 Planned and conducted sales drives that led to an increase in parents' attendance by 25% from the previous year